xcomment.com 2010-05-07

# Free Web Layouts - Myspace Layouts, Backgrounds, Graphics, Codes, & More!

This privacy policy has been made to provide information about our commitment to our visitors privacy while browsing our website.

**Information Automatically Logged  
**The only thing we log from our visitors are traffic statistics information and their IP address. The statistic information helps us see where our visitors are coming from and providing overall traffic analysis. IP addresses are logged for security reasons in helping us fix problems wrong with site.

**Third Party Sites**  
There are links to third party sites mainly from advertising companies bringing in traffic revenue. Freeweblayouts.net is not responsible for the content provided by these sites nor their privacy policy practices.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

**Personal Information**  
Freeweblayouts.net does not collect any personal information. This site will never ask visitors for their contact information (including email address). 

**Terms of Use**  
All content and services provided by Freeweblayouts.net are for personal use only. You may not distribute any content or services on this site without our written permission. Layouts and graphics design may not be modified and links to owners and back to freeweblayouts may not be removed. You may not use our content for unlawful purposes or anything prohibited by these terms and conditions.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, terms of use, or anything found on this site you can reach us 

[_here_](http://www.freeweblayouts.net/go.php?id=support).
